ELAVARASAN.G

HTML DEVELOPER&
PRODUCT ENGINEER

+91 9080278380

elaajay12@gmail.com

PROFILE

Committed professional offering more than 1+ years of experience in the field of Software development. Excellent communication skills and a consistent team player in all sorts of environments. Seeking to expand talents by bringing a wealth of expertise to a well-established company

CONTACT

Bargur BDO ofc OPP, Indra nagar, Krishnagiri Tamilnadu- 635104

Languages known

English, Tamil, Telugu

OPERATING SYSTEMS

Windows & IOS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, HTML 5

CSS, CSS 3

Bootstrap

JavaScript (Basic Knowledge)

SCSS/SASS

EXPERIENCE

Feb 2022 - Current

Product Engineer

SketchBrahma Technologies. Bangalore.

Maintained and ensured to enhance the company's multibrand website

Partnered with internal and external suppliers to create and maintain content. Assisted engineering team to define requirement from creative team on their Html pages

Jan 2021 - Feb 2022

HTML developer

Eooglo Technologies Pvt Ltd. Bangalore.

Writing cross-browser compliant HTML, CSS

Creating Email-templates & Email-alerts

Work collaboratively with design team to understand end user requirements to provide technical solutions and for the implementation of new software features

Build code that is easily readable, properly documented, and follows key coding standards

Developing and maintaining the front-end functionality of websites.

EDUCATION

2017- 2020

вса

AVS College of arts & science / Salem

Graduated with Computer Application branch from Periyar University College in year 2020 with 70CGPA

2015 - 2017

HigherSecondary

MTV Matric Higher Secondary School, krishnagiri

with 61%.